ourweddingday.com 2010-03-27

# OurWeddingDay: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out the type of personal information that we - OurWeddingDay.com, operated by OurWeddingDay.com LLC, which is a Limited Liability Company registered in Delaware - collect, what we use it for and the rights that you have in relation to this information. By using this Website and Wedding Websites, you accept the terms of this privacy policy.

1\. Collection of Personal Information

We shall collect personal information from you in a number of circumstances, including when you register your personal details, when you use our services, or when you enter any promotions at [www.OurWeddingDay.com](http://www.ourweddingday.com/). For example, when you register your personal details to create an Account, we ask for your name and email address as a minimum requirement. If you choose to purchase any service we will also ask for your credit or bank card details. Once you register and sign into your account or Wedding Website, you are not anonymous to us.

2\. Use of Personal Information

We will use your personal information for the purpose of providing the services offered through OurWeddingDay.com. We may collect information about your historical activity with us and your use of the Website and Wedding Websites. For example, we may record information on our servers from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the pages you visit.

When you register an Account or submit your personal information, we may choose to sell, exchange or rent your personal information (including your e-mail address) to third party partners (including David’s Bridal, Inc.), unless we believe that the release of this information is inappropriate. When you purchase services through the Website or Wedding Websites and enter payment information, this information may be transferred to the processing company for transaction authorization and authentication purposes.

We may send you information about services and features available on our Website or advice on how to use the various tools the site has to offer. We may also send you email communications and newsletters providing information and services offered by us and our partners.

You may not use the personal information of any Registered User of our Website, other than yourself, for any purpose whatsoever, whether personal or commercial. 

3\. Updating Personal Information

It is your responsibility to ensure that we have your correct contact information. This will enable us to provide you with the best service, Website and Wedding Website possible.

4\. Removal of Personal Information

If would like us to remove all the personal information we have about you from our records please send an email titled "unsubscribe" to [help@ourweddingday.com](mailto:help@ourweddingday.com). Please note that we require certain key information from you in order to provide you with our services, and if you ask us to remove all or part such information you may no longer be able to use or access the Website, Wedding Websites or parts of them.

5\. Minors

The consent of a parent or guardian shall be required before any child under the age of 18 can register their personal details. The parent or guardian will accept full responsibility for our use of this information, in accordance with this policy.

6\. Security

We will take reasonable precautions to ensure that all the personal information that you have submitted via the Website or Wedding Websites remains confidential. As required by United States state and federal law, we have strict security procedures regarding the storage and disclosure of personal information. However, we may be required by law to disclose such personal information to proper law enforcement authorities, including to the United States Government. Further, if we merge with, or are acquired by, another company, the resulting combined company may use the personal information that you have submitted, as described in this policy. If we cease operation, your personal information may be transferred to and used by another company that offers similar or related products or services.

7\. Transfer of Data

In order to provide you with certain services and/or products we may need to transfer your personal information outside the USA, where data protection laws may not be comparable to those within the USA. By submitting your personal information to us you consent to such a transfer.

8\. Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and Revisions

This policy forms part of our Terms of Use which governs your use of this Website and Wedding Websites we provide (both of which may be changed or updated from time to time without notice). By using the Website and Wedding Websites you are deemed to accept the Terms of Use and the terms and conditions of this policy. Our use of your personal information is subject to the terms and conditions of our policy in force at the time when we use the information in question. 

Last Updated on November 19, 2009
